So now you know on parent's
day, when we have parents here,
we had the two sheets of glass.
One is called annealed.
It just means it's not
tempered, and the baseball
was supposed to break it.
It didn't.
Peter's got very
good annealed glass.
He's the one that gave
us those big sheets.
And it breaks into these
huge, dangerous shards.
Thanks, Peter.
Take care.
Oh yeah, thank you.
[APPLAUSE]
If you notice, the tempered
glass, we tried to break it.
It also doesn't break.
It was supposed to be the
only one that didn't break.
But then you take a
little hammer at the edge
and you just lightly tap
the edge and the whole thing
breaks.
Why?
Because it's got so
much built-in stress.
It's got all this
compressive stress,
and the edge isn't
protecting that.
The edge of that tempered glass
isn't protecting the stress.
So when I just dig
in a little bit,
it's able to all crack
and release that stress.
So that's what
happened on family day.
Here's a high-speed video.
These are two guys from Corning.
And we can listen to this.
[VIDEO PLAYBACK]
They're actually pretty cool.